http://humanities.osu.edu/privacy-policy

Search
AboutAbout the CollegeCollege DirectoryOffice of the DeanDean's External Advisory CommitteeStaff Advisory CouncilStrategic PlanNotable AlumniCollege HistoryCommitted to Diversity, Equity and InclusionCertificate ProgramDepartments & CentersHonors & RecognitionFacilitiesAbout ColumbusFor Faculty & StaffAcademicsAcademic ProgramsCertificatesDiversity, Equity and Inclusion CertificateEssential Skills for Travel and Business in Russia CertificateHealth Communication CertificateScience and Environmental Communication CertificateTranslation and Interpretation CertificateExplore Our ProgramsDepartments & CentersFuture StudentsWhy Arts and Sciences?Your JourneyExperience the Arts and Sciences VirtuallyVirtual Academic OverviewsBuckeye LifeProgram for Advancing Scholarship and Service (PASS)Admissions InformationFrequently Asked QuestionsContact UsAcademic ContactsFor High School CounselorsCurrent StudentsAdvising & Academics2020 OrientationAdvising SupportGeneral Education RequirementsCourse SchedulingAdding & Dropping CoursesHonors & ScholarsDegree PlanningDeclare Your MajorGraduation & Research DistinctionPoliciesCapital ProgramAdministrationBeyond the ClassroomInternshipsEducation AbroadUndergraduate ResearchVolunteeringService LearningPeer MentoringStudent LeadershipScholarships & GrantsMerit & Need-Based AwardsResearch & Creative Activity FundingEducation Abroad FundingDiversity ScholarshipsGet InvolvedUndergraduate Student e-NewsletterTake Your Professor To Lunch ProgramArts and Sciences Student OrganizationsArts and Sciences Student CouncilArts and Sciences Dean's Student Advisory BoardDiversity MattersStudent ResourcesGraduate StudentsGraduate ProgramsFunding ResourcesDiversity in Graduate StudiesDiscovery Scholars ProgramGraduate Student AwardsCollege Credit Plus Teacher Credentialing ProgramsNews & EventsSubscribeResponding to a PandemicNewsThe Daily PostWeekly News & UpdatesExperts in the MediaSpotlightsInsightEventsPodcastsASCENT MagazineSocial Media & PublicationsCareer SuccessHandshakeStudent AccessEligibilityUser GuidesBeyond HandshakeEmployer AccessEventsCareer FairsStudentsBeyond the ClassroomPersonalize Your Career PlanNavigating the Career Planning ProcessGuides & Tip SheetsFavorite LinksCareer ReadinessOther ResourcesChat with a Career Coach!Career Accelerator FundDiscover VMockCareer Success: Temporary ChangesOffice PoliciesCareer CommunitiesEmployersRecruiting OptionsOffice PoliciesVisiting CampusAlumniStaying InvolvedRecruiting StudentsRecent Grad ServicesAlumni SpotlightsConnectFor Faculty & StaffResearchCommunity OutreachDepartments & CentersUndergraduate ResearchScience SundaysBusiness OpportunitiesArtsArts & Culture in the CollegeGalleries, Museums & CollectionsDepartments & CentersVenues & ParkingVirtual Arts GalleryArts DistrictUpcoming EventsInaugural LecturesAlumni & GivingGiving in Arts & SciencesHow to GiveNews & EventsASCENT MagazineConnect NewsletterArchiveVirtual Events ArchivePhoto GalleryVolunteer OpportunitiesShare Your StoriesAlumni SocietyStudent Ambassador Program ApplicationAbout Our AlumniNotable AlumniAlumni AwardsCall for NominationsSearch
You are hereHome / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Policy OverviewCollege of Arts and Sciences at The Ohio State University recognize the importance of privacy to visitors of our Web sites. This privacy policy explains what type of information is collected from you when you visit any of the colleges websites.Visitors under the age of 18 must obtain permission from their parents or guardians before sending any personal identifying information to any College of Arts and Sciences website.College of Arts and Sciences are committed to ensuring the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information. We do not actively share personal information gathered from our Web servers. However, because the College of Arts and Sciences is a public institutions, some information collected from the colleges websites, including information from our server logs, e-mails delivered to our websites, and information collected from Web-based forms, may be subject to the Ohio Public Records Act. This means that while we do not actively share information, in some cases we may be compelled by law to release information gathered from our Web servers.College of Arts and Sciences also comply with The Ohio State University's Policy concerning Privacy and Release of Student Education Records.What Information is Collected?All College of Arts and Sciences websites track IP address information to improve functionality and content, and to monitor the site's performance. Data is used to provide answers to specific questions about the usage and performance of the website or individual Web pages. Except as defined above, no IP address data is shared with parties external to the University.Some pages within the College of Arts and Sciences Web sites require personal information in order to provide online services. Personal information is gathered and stored in a secure manner to prevent monitoring or interception. Arts and Sciences and their designated online service providers do not share personal information with third parties except as defined above.Like all other Web servers, College of Arts and Sciences Web servers automatically create log files for each visitor who accesses our site. These "access logs" allow us to make our site more useful to our visitors. The access logs do NOT record a visitor's name, address, phone number, credit card numbers, or any other personal identifying information. Rather, they contain some or all of the following information:The Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of machines which accessed our website.The date of the visit.The time of the visit.The path taken through our website.The browser being used.A list of files downloaded or viewed.Any errors encountered.All of the information collected by the College of Arts and Sciences are used for internal purposes only and is not distributed to any other charitable, cultural, nonprofit organizations or parties outside The Ohio State University.Updates and Contact InformationThe College of Arts and Sciences along with The Ohio State University reserve the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of any College of Arts and Sciences websites constitutes consent to any policy then in effect.Disclaimer of LiabilityThe information contained in this policy explains the Internet privacy policy and practices that the College of Arts and Sciences at The Ohio State University have adopted for their official Web pages. In legal terms, it shall not be construed as a contractual promise, and the college reserves the right to amend it at any time without notice. Neither the College of Arts and Sciences nor any of its units, programs, employees, agents, or individual trustees shall be held liable for any improper or incorrect use of the information described and/or contained in the college website and assumes no responsibility for anyone's use of the information.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us via e-mail at asccomm@osu.edu.
Office of the Dean
(614) 292-1667
186 University Hall
230 North Oval Mall
Columbus, OH 43210
Advising Office
(614) 292-6961
100 Denney Hall
164 Annie & John Glenn Ave.
If you have a disability and experience difficulty accessing this site,
please contact us for assistance via email at asc-accessibility@osu.edu.
© 2020 The Ohio State University College Of The Arts And Sciences
Privacy Policy
Login
Top
